If looks could kill.
The Lookalike is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by Richard Gray.
Two crooks looking out for a drug lord's love interest scramble
to find a look-alike after she dies unexpectedly.
Holt Mulligan, played by Justin Long.
Joe Mulligan, played by Jerry O'Connell.
Lacey, played by Gillian Jacobs.
Mila, played by Scottie Thompson.
Lee Garner, played by Gina Gershon.
Bobby, played by John Corbett.
The Lookalike is a 2014 American crime thriller film directed
by Richard Gray and written by Michele Gray.
The film stars Justin Long, Jerry O'Connell, Gillian Jacobs, Scottie Thompson, John
Corbett, Gina Gershon, Steven Bauer, John Savage, and Luis Guzmán.
It was released in the United States on November 7,
2014, by Well Go USA Entertainment.
The tone is emotional and intense.